http://www.centralnational.com/privacy-internet.asp

Savings & Money Market
It Makes ¢ents!
Raymond James Financial Services
Why Central?
Locations
Where can we help you?
Locations
888.262.5456
Technology
Old bank, new tech.
History
Dedicated to you since 1884.
Rewards
Benefits you'll use.
Services
What else can we do for you?
Effective 12/19/2019
This financial institution recognizes the importance our customers place on privacy and the security of their personal information. Our goal is to protect your personal information in every way that we interact with you, including on the Internet.
We think it is important for you to be informed of the policies, procedures, and security measures we have in place to safeguard your personal and confidential information. We have developed a policy statement to help you to understand the steps we take to protect your personal information.
Privacy Updates
New product releases may require changes to our Privacy Practices. In the event we begin to share nonpublic personal information in a manner that would require a revision to our Privacy Practices an updated Privacy Notice will be provided to you in accordance with the timing and delivery constraints outlined within appropriate banking regulations.
We reserve the right to make changes to our Internet Privacy Notice at any time and for any reason without prior notice.
Online Banking Security
For information regarding the security of Central Online Banking, view our Sign In Security.
External 3rd Party Links
We do offer links to other 3rd party sites. These links to external third parties are offered as a courtesy and a convenience to our customers. This financial institution is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites' service providers.
Third party merchants may collect personal information from you when you visit their sites. For example, they collect personal information from you when you provide billing information or send them an email. Some third party merchants may also send you a cookie to collect data on your Internet usage and preferences. When you click on advertisements at third party sites, the advertising company may also send you a cookie. This financial institution does NOT have access to the information collected by any third party, nor can we control how they use this information. As a general rule, you should always look for and review a site's privacy policy before giving out any personal information.
If you have questions or concerns about the privacy policies and practices of these third parties, please review their websites and contact them directly. Central National Bank assumes no responsibility for the content, safety, security, or privacy of any such site or any transactions you conduct through them.
Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're on the Internet. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.
What is a Cookie?
A cookie is a very small text file sent by a web server and stored on your hard disk on in your browser so that it can be read back later. Cookies cannot "read" information about you from your computer or be used to "steal" information about you; cookies don't carry viruses; and cookies are not programs that can perform functions on your computer.
Cookies are a basic way for a server to identify you (most cookies actually identify the computer you happen to be using at the time, not you personally), and cookies are used for many things from personalizing start up pages to facilitating online purchases. Cookies do perform a very important function when you engage in secure Internet banking. The cookies used in our Internet banking system are described below.
Website Visitors
Visitors to our website remain anonymous. We do not collect unique identifying information about you unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us that information, such as when you send us an email or complete an application online. If you provide us this information, it is only used internally and in furtherance of the purpose for which it was provided. Central National Bank may use “cookies” to provide advertisements similar to products you have viewed on our company website. Disabling cookies in your browser may cause you to not receive advertising or other offers from us that are relevant to your interests and needs. If you are an Internet banking customer, NetTeller (our Central Online Banking provider) will send you a cookie for security purposes.
Information That We Collect:
In the course of providing our services to you, we collect "nonpublic personal information" -- information about you that is not available publicly, from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications, emails, or other forms;
Information about your transactions with us and others;
Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency; and
Information that is generated when you contact us electronically or visit pages on our website and blog.
Disclosure of Information
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone, except as permitted by law. We may disclose all the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We must provide certain customer account information to financial service providers such as Jack Henry & Associates so that we may process your banking transactions.
We do not sell any of your personal information.
We will not disclose any medical information that you provide to us, unless you specifically authorize its disclosure.
Fair Credit Reporting Act
The Fair Credit Reporting Act does allow us to share within our organization information concerning your transactions and experiences. This could involve, for example, information such as your name, address or type of account being shared with an affiliated insurance agent. We would do this only to provide you with information regarding products and services you may have an interest in, or to explore product pricing that may be to your benefit.
Security
This financial institution has developed strict policies and procedures to safeguard your personal information. We restrict employee access to your nonpublic personal information to a "need to know" basis. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. We educate our employees about the importance of confidentiality and customer privacy. We take appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce employee privacy responsibilities.
We offer secure email through our Internet banking services. You should use the secure mail service anytime you send us sensitive personal information.
Our Internet banking service provider, Jack Henry & Associates, has also developed security policies and procedures to protect the customer information that they must collect and maintain to help us process your banking transactions over the Internet. They have developed a top-of-the line security system to ensure your customer information is protected on the Internet and within the Jack Henry & Associates environment.
Questions
If you would like to know what information we have collected in connection with your use of our products and services, including Internet based products and services, please contact us at 1-888-262-5456 8:00 am - 5:30 pm CST Monday-Friday.
After reviewing the information, if you believe any of the information is in error, contact us either by phone or email, info@centralnational.com, or send a letter that explains the alleged discrepancy. If the information is incorrect, we will work with you to ensure your information is promptly updated.
In addition, if you believe any information that Central National Bank has collected about you has been used for an improper purpose, please contact us at info@centralnational.com.
Explain your concerns in as much detail as possible so that we may take any appropriate action.
This website is not targeted or marketed to children.
You can provide information at our website to open Youth accounts, however, we require that a qualified joint applicant at least 18 years of age submit the enrollment information. We feel strongly about protecting the privacy of children and teenagers. As such, we do not knowingly collect information from persons under the age of 18 through this website. However, individuals within this age group could register for online accounts with the assistance of someone 18 years of age or older.
How can we help?
Let us know the best way to reach you and one of our customer representatives will be in touch.
Contact Us
Open Account
© 2020 Central National Bank. All rights reserved.
Facebook
Twitter
Secure Page Sign-In
Ensuring the security of your personal information is important to us.
When you sign in to Online Banking on our home page, your User Name and Password are secure. The moment you click the Log In button, we encrypt your user name and password using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.
Browser Security Indicators
You may notice when you are on our home page that some familiar indicators do not appear in your browser to confirm the entire page is secure. Those indicators include the small "lock" icon in the bottom right corner of the browser frame and the "s" in the Web address bar (for example, "https").
To provide the fast access to our home page, we have made signing in to Online Banking secure without making the entire page secure. You can be assured that your ID and password are secure and that only Central National Bank has access to them.
Centralnational.com is SSL-Encypted
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology secretly encodes (encrypts data) information that is being sent over the Internet between your computer and Central National Bank, helping to ensure that the information remains confidential.
×
Leaving Site
You have requested a web page that is external to the Central National Bank (CNB) web site.
The operator of the site you are entering may have a privacy policy different than CNB.
CNB does not endorse or monitor this web site and has no control over its content or offerings.
It Makes ¢ents!
Why Central?
